(Sheldon:)only my name is
on the cable bill?
(Leonard:)Yeah.
(Sheldon:)Good, good.
(Sheldon:)And your name is
on the electric bill
(Sheldon:)and mine isn't.
(Sheldon:)And I'm okay with that.
(Leonard:)Actually, your name is
on the electric bill.
(Sheldon:)Oh, right.
(Sheldon:)This is a disaster.
(Leonard:)I don't even know what you're
talking about and I agree.
(Sheldon:)Okay, I have
to tell you something,
(Sheldon:)but you're not going to like it.
(Leonard:)What's going on?
(Sheldon:)An article was just published
in Scientific American
about our theory.
(Leonard:)Did they hate it?
(Sheldon:)No. No, they loved it.
(Sheldon:)They, uh, couldn't say enough
nice things about it.
(Leonard:)So what's the problem?
You know how the PennySaver
only has my name...
Sheldon!
(Sheldon:)They didn't mention you
in the article.
(Sheldon:)Only me.